{
    "subject": "Luis_Bay\u00f3n_Herrera",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Jettatore",
    "human_readable": "Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Jettatore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8491269946098328,
            "question": "Who created Jettatore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7592365741729736,
            "question": "What did Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera invent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7492018938064575,
            "question": "Who is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7372462749481201,
            "question": "What else might Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera have created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7245653867721558,
            "question": "What is the name of the creation by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978538990020752,
            "question": "Is Jettatore a known invention?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46562081575393677,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Jettatore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4535899758338928,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Jettatore's purpose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4322047829627991,
            "question": "What field is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3957310914993286,
            "question": "What is known about Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Jettatore.",
            "html": "yago_12704_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera known for?",
            "html": "yago_12704_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Jettatore's purpose?",
            "html": "yago_12704_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Jettatore?",
            "html": "yago_12704_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12704_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe documents state that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera was a director known for the film *Jettatore* (1938). This supports the claim that he created it.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera was a director and writer, known for Buenos Aires a la vista (1950), Jettatore (1938) and Una cubana en Espa\u00f1a (1951). Therefore, the information supports the triple that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created Jettatore."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera was a director and are associated with film works such as \"Buenos Aires a la vista (1950)\", \"Jettatore (1938)\", and \"Una cubana en Espa\u00f1a (1951)\". While the specific film \"Jettatore\" is not mentioned directly, it is reasonable to infer that Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera created or directed films, which includes creating cinematic works like \"Jettatore\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}